{
	"description": "Kanji for JLPT N5",
	"deck": [
	{ "question": "お兄さん", "answers":[ "おにいさん" ] },
	{ "question": "お姉さん", "answers":[ "おねえさん" ] },
	{ "question": "お弁当", "answers":[ "おべんとう" ] },
	{ "question": "お手洗い", "answers":[ "おてあらい" ] },
	{ "question": "お母さん", "answers":[ "おかあさん" ] },
	{ "question": "母", "answers":[ "はは" ] },
	{ "question": "お父さん", "answers":[ "おとうさん" ] },
	{ "question": "父", "answers":[ "ちち" ] },
	{ "question": "お皿", "answers":[ "おさら" ] },
	{ "question": "お茶", "answers":[ "おちゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "お菓子", "answers":[ "おかし" ] },
	{ "question": "お酒", "answers":[ "おさけ" ] },
	{ "question": "お金", "answers":[ "おかね" ] },
	{ "question": "お風呂", "answers":[ "おふろ" ] },
	{ "question": "さ来年", "answers":[ "さらいねん" ] },
	{ "question": "とり肉", "answers":[ "とりにく" ] },
	{ "question": "もう一度", "answers":[ "もういちど" ] },
	{ "question": "一", "answers":[ "いち" ] },
	{ "question": "一つ", "answers":[ "ひとつ" ] },
	{ "question": "一人", "answers":[ "ひとり" ] },
	{ "question": "一日", "answers":[ "ついたち", "いちにち" ] },
	{ "question": "一昨年", "answers":[ "おととし" ] },
	{ "question": "一昨日", "answers":[ "おととい" ] },
	{ "question": "一月", "answers":[ "ひとつき", "いちがつ" ] },
	{ "question": "一緒", "answers":[ "いっしょ" ] },
	{ "question": "七", "answers":[ "なな", "しち" ] },
	{ "question": "七つ", "answers":[ "ななつ" ] },
	{ "question": "七日", "answers":[ "なのか" ] },
	{ "question": "万", "answers":[ "まん" ] },
	{ "question": "万年筆", "answers":[ "まんねんひつ" ] },
	{ "question": "丈夫", "answers":[ "じょうぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "円", "answers":[ "えん", "まる" ] },
	{ "question": "三", "answers":[ "さん" ] },
	{ "question": "三つ", "answers":[ "みっつ" ] },
	{ "question": "三日", "answers":[ "みっか" ] },
	{ "question": "上", "answers":[ "うえ", "かみ" ] },
	{ "question": "上手", "answers":[ "じょうず", "うわて", "かみて" ] },
	{ "question": "上着", "answers":[ "うわぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "下", "answers":[ "した", "もと", "しも" ] },
	{ "question": "下手", "answers":[ "へた" ] },
	{ "question": "両親", "answers":[ "りょうしん" ] },
	{ "question": "並ぶ", "answers":[ "ならぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "並べる", "answers":[ "ならべる" ] },
	{ "question": "中", "answers":[ "なか" ] },
	{ "question": "乗る", "answers":[ "のる" ] },
	{ "question": "九", "answers":[ "きゅう", "く" ] },
	{ "question": "九つ", "answers":[ "ここのつ" ] },
	{ "question": "九日", "answers":[ "ここのか" ] },
	{ "question": "二", "answers":[ "に" ] },
	{ "question": "二つ", "answers":[ "ふたつ" ] },
	{ "question": "二人", "answers":[ "ふたり" ] },
	{ "question": "二十日", "answers":[ "はつか" ] },
	{ "question": "二十歳", "answers":[ "はたち" ] },
	{ "question": "二日", "answers":[ "ふつか" ] },
	{ "question": "五", "answers":[ "ご" ] },
	{ "question": "五つ", "answers":[ "いつつ" ] },
	{ "question": "五日", "answers":[ "いつか" ] },
	{ "question": "交差点", "answers":[ "こうさてん" ] },
	{ "question": "交番", "answers":[ "こうばん" ] },
	{ "question": "人", "answers":[ "ひと" ] },
	{ "question": "今", "answers":[ "いま" ] },
	{ "question": "今年", "answers":[ "ことし" ] },
	{ "question": "今日", "answers":[ "きょう" ] },
	{ "question": "今晩", "answers":[ "こんばん" ] },
	{ "question": "今月", "answers":[ "こんげつ" ] },
	{ "question": "今朝", "answers":[ "けさ" ] },
	{ "question": "今週", "answers":[ "こんしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "仕事", "answers":[ "しごと" ] },
	{ "question": "休み", "answers":[ "やすみ" ] },
	{ "question": "休む", "answers":[ "やすむ" ] },
	{ "question": "会社", "answers":[ "かいしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "低い", "answers":[ "ひくい" ] },
	{ "question": "住む", "answers":[ "すむ" ] },
	{ "question": "体", "answers":[ "からだ" ] },
	{ "question": "作る", "answers":[ "つくる" ] },
	{ "question": "作文", "answers":[ "さくぶん" ] },
	{ "question": "使う", "answers":[ "つかう" ] },
	{ "question": "便利", "answers":[ "べんり" ] },
	{ "question": "借りる", "answers":[ "かりる" ] },
	{ "question": "傘", "answers":[ "かさ" ] },
	{ "question": "働く", "answers":[ "はたらく" ] },
	{ "question": "元気", "answers":[ "げんき" ] },
	{ "question": "兄", "answers":[ "あに" ] },
	{ "question": "兄弟", "answers":[ "きょうだい" ] },
	{ "question": "先", "answers":[ "さき", "せん" ] },
	{ "question": "先月", "answers":[ "せんげつ" ] },
	{ "question": "先生", "answers":[ "せんせい" ] },
	{ "question": "先週", "answers":[ "せんしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "入る", "answers":[ "はいる", "いる" ] },
	{ "question": "入れる", "answers":[ "いれる" ] },
	{ "question": "入口", "answers":[ "いりぐち" ] },
	{ "question": "全部", "answers":[ "ぜんぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "八", "answers":[ "はち" ] },
	{ "question": "八つ", "answers":[ "やっつ" ] },
	{ "question": "八日", "answers":[ "ようか" ] },
	{ "question": "公園", "answers":[ "こうえん" ] },
	{ "question": "六", "answers":[ "ろく" ] },
	{ "question": "六つ", "answers":[ "むっつ" ] },
	{ "question": "六日", "answers":[ "むいか" ] },
	{ "question": "写真", "answers":[ "しゃしん" ] },
	{ "question": "冬", "answers":[ "ふゆ" ] },
	{ "question": "出かける", "answers":[ "でかける" ] },
	{ "question": "出す", "answers":[ "だす" ] },
	{ "question": "出る", "answers":[ "でる" ] },
	{ "question": "出口", "answers":[ "でぐち" ] },
	{ "question": "分かる", "answers":[ "わかる" ] },
	{ "question": "切る", "answers":[ "きる" ] },
	{ "question": "切手", "answers":[ "きって" ] },
	{ "question": "切符", "answers":[ "きっぷ" ] },
	{ "question": "初めて", "answers":[ "はじめて" ] },
	{ "question": "前", "answers":[ "まえ" ] },
	{ "question": "動物", "answers":[ "どうぶつ" ] },
	{ "question": "北", "answers":[ "きた" ] },
	{ "question": "医者", "answers":[ "いしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "十日", "answers":[ "とおか" ] },
	{ "question": "千", "answers":[ "せん" ] },
	{ "question": "午前", "answers":[ "ごぜん" ] },
	{ "question": "午後", "answers":[ "ごご" ] },
	{ "question": "半", "answers":[ "はん" ] },
	{ "question": "半分", "answers":[ "はんぶん" ] },
	{ "question": "南", "answers":[ "みなみ" ] },
	{ "question": "去年", "answers":[ "きょねん" ] },
	{ "question": "友達", "answers":[ "ともだち" ] },
	{ "question": "取る", "answers":[ "とる" ] },
	{ "question": "口", "answers":[ "くち" ] },
	{ "question": "古い", "answers":[ "ふるい" ] },
	{ "question": "台所", "answers":[ "だいどころ" ] },
	{ "question": "右", "answers":[ "みぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "同じ", "answers":[ "おなじ" ] },
	{ "question": "名前", "answers":[ "なまえ" ] },
	{ "question": "向こう", "answers":[ "むこう" ] },
	{ "question": "吸う", "answers":[ "すう" ] },
	{ "question": "吹く", "answers":[ "ふく" ] },
	{ "question": "呼ぶ", "answers":[ "よぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "咲く", "answers":[ "さく" ] },
	{ "question": "問題", "answers":[ "もんだい" ] },
	{ "question": "四", "answers":[ "よん", "し" ] },
	{ "question": "四つ", "answers":[ "よっつ" ] },
	{ "question": "四日", "answers":[ "よっか" ] },
	{ "question": "国", "answers":[ "くに" ] },
	{ "question": "土", "answers":[ "つち" ] },
	{ "question": "土曜日", "answers":[ "どようび" ] },
	{ "question": "地下鉄", "answers":[ "ちかてつ" ] },
	{ "question": "地図", "answers":[ "ちず" ] },
	{ "question": "売る", "answers":[ "うる" ] },
	{ "question": "夏", "answers":[ "なつ" ] },
	{ "question": "夏休み", "answers":[ "なつやすみ" ] },
	{ "question": "夕方", "answers":[ "ゆうがた" ] },
	{ "question": "夕飯", "answers":[ "ゆうはん" ] },
	{ "question": "外", "answers":[ "そと", "ほか" ] },
	{ "question": "外国", "answers":[ "がいこく" ] },
	{ "question": "外国人", "answers":[ "がいこくじん" ] },
	{ "question": "多い", "answers":[ "おおい" ] },
	{ "question": "夜", "answers":[ "よる" ] },
	{ "question": "大きい", "answers":[ "おおきい" ] },
	{ "question": "大きな", "answers":[ "おおきな" ] },
	{ "question": "大丈夫", "answers":[ "だいじょうぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "大人", "answers":[ "おとな" ] },
	{ "question": "大使館", "answers":[ "たいしかん" ] },
	{ "question": "大切", "answers":[ "たいせつ" ] },
	{ "question": "大勢", "answers":[ "おおぜい" ] },
	{ "question": "大好き", "answers":[ "だいすき" ] },
	{ "question": "大学", "answers":[ "だいがく" ] },
	{ "question": "天気", "answers":[ "てんき" ] },
	{ "question": "太い", "answers":[ "ふとい" ] },
	{ "question": "奥さん", "answers":[ "おくさん" ] },
	{ "question": "女", "answers":[ "おんな" ] },
	{ "question": "女の子", "answers":[ "おんなのこ" ] },
	{ "question": "好き", "answers":[ "すき" ] },
	{ "question": "妹", "answers":[ "いもうと" ] },
	{ "question": "姉", "answers":[ "あね" ] },
	{ "question": "始まる", "answers":[ "はじまる" ] },
	{ "question": "子供", "answers":[ "こども" ] },
	{ "question": "字引", "answers":[ "じびき" ] },
	{ "question": "学校", "answers":[ "がっこう" ] },
	{ "question": "学生", "answers":[ "がくせい" ] },
	{ "question": "安い", "answers":[ "やすい" ] },
	{ "question": "家", "answers":[ "いえ" ] },
	{ "question": "家庭", "answers":[ "かてい" ] },
	{ "question": "家族", "answers":[ "かぞく" ] },
	{ "question": "宿題", "answers":[ "しゅくだい" ] },
	{ "question": "寒い", "answers":[ "さむい" ] },
	{ "question": "寝る", "answers":[ "ねる" ] },
	{ "question": "小さい", "answers":[ "ちいさい" ] },
	{ "question": "小さな", "answers":[ "ちいさな" ] },
	{ "question": "少し", "answers":[ "すこし" ] },
	{ "question": "少ない", "answers":[ "すくない" ] },
	{ "question": "居る", "answers":[ "いる" ] },
	{ "question": "山", "answers":[ "やま" ] },
	{ "question": "川", "answers":[ "かわ" ] },
	{ "question": "左", "answers":[ "ひだり" ] },
	{ "question": "差す", "answers":[ "さす" ] },
	{ "question": "帰る", "answers":[ "かえる" ] },
	{ "question": "年", "answers":[ "とし" ] },
	{ "question": "広い", "answers":[ "ひろい" ] },
	{ "question": "店", "answers":[ "みせ" ] },
	{ "question": "座る", "answers":[ "すわる" ] },
	{ "question": "庭", "answers":[ "にわ" ] },
	{ "question": "廊下", "answers":[ "ろうか" ] },
	{ "question": "建物", "answers":[ "たてもの" ] },
	{ "question": "引く", "answers":[ "ひく" ] },
	{ "question": "弟", "answers":[ "おとうと" ] },
	{ "question": "弱い", "answers":[ "よわい" ] },
	{ "question": "強い", "answers":[ "つよい" ] },
	{ "question": "弾く", "answers":[ "ひく", "はじく" ] },
	{ "question": "待つ", "answers":[ "まつ" ] },
	{ "question": "後", "answers":[ "あと", "のち" ] },
	{ "question": "後ろ", "answers":[ "うしろ" ] },
	{ "question": "ご飯", "answers":[ "ごはん" ] },
	{ "question": "忘れる", "answers":[ "わすれる" ] },
	{ "question": "忙しい", "answers":[ "いそがしい" ] },
	{ "question": "悪い", "answers":[ "わるい" ] },
	{ "question": "意味", "answers":[ "いみ" ] },
	{ "question": "戸", "answers":[ "と" ] },
	{ "question": "所", "answers":[ "ところ" ] },
	{ "question": "手", "answers":[ "て" ] },
	{ "question": "手紙", "answers":[ "てがみ" ] },
	{ "question": "押す", "answers":[ "おす" ] },
	{ "question": "持つ", "answers":[ "もつ" ] },
	{ "question": "教える", "answers":[ "おしえる" ] },
	{ "question": "教室", "answers":[ "きょうしつ" ] },
	{ "question": "散歩", "answers":[ "さんぽ" ] },
	{ "question": "文章", "answers":[ "ぶんしょう" ] },
	{ "question": "料理", "answers":[ "りょうり" ] },
	{ "question": "新しい", "answers":[ "あたらしい" ] },
	{ "question": "新聞", "answers":[ "しんぶん" ] },
	{ "question": "方", "answers":[ "かた" ] },
	{ "question": "旅行", "answers":[ "りょこう" ] },
	{ "question": "日曜日", "answers":[ "にちようび" ] },
	{ "question": "早い", "answers":[ "はやい" ] },
	{ "question": "映画", "answers":[ "えいが" ] },
	{ "question": "映画館", "answers":[ "えいがかん" ] },
	{ "question": "春", "answers":[ "はる" ] },
	{ "question": "昨夜", "answers":[ "さくや", "ゆうべ" ] },
	{ "question": "昨日", "answers":[ "きのう" ] },
	{ "question": "昼", "answers":[ "ひる" ] },
	{ "question": "昼御飯", "answers":[ "ひるごはん" ] },
	{ "question": "時", "answers":[ "とき" ] },
	{ "question": "時々", "answers":[ "ときどき" ] },
	{ "question": "時計", "answers":[ "とけい" ] },
	{ "question": "間", "answers":[ "あいだ", "ま", "かん" ] },
	{ "question": "時間", "answers":[ "じかん" ] },
	{ "question": "晩", "answers":[ "ばん" ] },
	{ "question": "晩御飯", "answers":[ "ばんごはん" ] },
	{ "question": "晴れ", "answers":[ "はれ" ] },
	{ "question": "晴れる", "answers":[ "はれる" ] },
	{ "question": "暇", "answers":[ "ひま" ] },
	{ "question": "暑い", "answers":[ "あつい" ] },
	{ "question": "暗い", "answers":[ "くらい" ] },
	{ "question": "曇り", "answers":[ "くもり" ] },
	{ "question": "曇る", "answers":[ "くもる" ] },
	{ "question": "曲る", "answers":[ "まがる" ] },
	{ "question": "書く", "answers":[ "かく" ] },
	{ "question": "月", "answers":[ "つき" ] },
	{ "question": "月曜日", "answers":[ "げつようび" ] },
	{ "question": "有名", "answers":[ "ゆうめい" ] },
	{ "question": "服", "answers":[ "ふく" ] },
	{ "question": "木", "answers":[ "き" ] },
	{ "question": "木曜日", "answers":[ "もくようび" ] },
	{ "question": "本", "answers":[ "ほん" ] },
	{ "question": "村", "answers":[ "むら" ] },
	{ "question": "来る", "answers":[ "くる", "きたる" ] },
	{ "question": "来年", "answers":[ "らいねん" ] },
	{ "question": "来月", "answers":[ "らいげつ" ] },
	{ "question": "来週", "answers":[ "らいしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "東", "answers":[ "ひがし" ] },
	{ "question": "果物", "answers":[ "くだもの" ] },
	{ "question": "楽しい", "answers":[ "たのしい" ] },
	{ "question": "横", "answers":[ "よこ" ] },
	{ "question": "橋", "answers":[ "はし" ] },
	{ "question": "次", "answers":[ "つぎ" ] },
	{ "question": "欲しい", "answers":[ "ほしい" ] },
	{ "question": "歌", "answers":[ "うた" ] },
	{ "question": "歌う", "answers":[ "うたう" ] },
	{ "question": "止まる", "answers":[ "とまる" ] },
	{ "question": "歩く", "answers":[ "あるく" ] },
	{ "question": "歯", "answers":[ "は" ] },
	{ "question": "死ぬ", "answers":[ "しぬ" ] },
	{ "question": "毎日", "answers":[ "まいにち" ] },
	{ "question": "毎晩", "answers":[ "まいばん" ] },
	{ "question": "毎朝", "answers":[ "まいあさ" ] },
	{ "question": "毎週", "answers":[ "まいしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "水", "answers":[ "みず" ] },
	{ "question": "水曜日", "answers":[ "すいようび" ] },
	{ "question": "汚い", "answers":[ "きたない" ] },
	{ "question": "池", "answers":[ "いけ" ] },
	{ "question": "泳ぐ", "answers":[ "およぐ" ] },
	{ "question": "洋服", "answers":[ "ようふく" ] },
	{ "question": "洗う", "answers":[ "あらう" ] },
	{ "question": "洗濯", "answers":[ "せんたく" ] },
	{ "question": "海", "answers":[ "うみ" ] },
	{ "question": "消える", "answers":[ "きえる" ] },
	{ "question": "消す", "answers":[ "けす" ] },
	{ "question": "涼しい", "answers":[ "すずしい" ] },
	{ "question": "温い", "answers":[ "ぬるい" ] },
	{ "question": "漢字", "answers":[ "かんじ" ] },
	{ "question": "火", "answers":[ "ひ" ] },
	{ "question": "火曜日", "answers":[ "かようび" ] },
	{ "question": "灰皿", "answers":[ "はいざら" ] },
	{ "question": "無くす", "answers":[ "なくす" ] },
	{ "question": "熱い", "answers":[ "あつい" ] },
	{ "question": "牛乳", "answers":[ "ぎゅうにゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "牛肉", "answers":[ "ぎゅうにく" ] },
	{ "question": "物", "answers":[ "もの" ] },
	{ "question": "犬", "answers":[ "いぬ" ] },
	{ "question": "狭い", "answers":[ "せまい" ] },
	{ "question": "猫", "answers":[ "ねこ" ] },
	{ "question": "玄関", "answers":[ "げんかん" ] },
	{ "question": "甘い", "answers":[ "あまい" ] },
	{ "question": "生まれる", "answers":[ "うまれる" ] },
	{ "question": "生きる", "answers":[ "いきる" ] },
	{ "question": "生徒", "answers":[ "せいと" ] },
	{ "question": "男", "answers":[ "おとこ" ] },
	{ "question": "男の子", "answers":[ "おとこのこ" ] },
	{ "question": "町", "answers":[ "まち" ] },
	{ "question": "留学生", "answers":[ "りゅうがくせい" ] },
	{ "question": "番号", "answers":[ "ばんごう" ] },
	{ "question": "疲れる", "answers":[ "つかれる" ] },
	{ "question": "病気", "answers":[ "びょうき" ] },
	{ "question": "病院", "answers":[ "びょういん" ] },
	{ "question": "痛い", "answers":[ "いたい" ] },
	{ "question": "登る", "answers":[ "のぼる" ] },
	{ "question": "白", "answers":[ "しろ" ] },
	{ "question": "白い", "answers":[ "しろい" ] },
	{ "question": "百", "answers":[ "ひゃく" ] },
	{ "question": "皆さん", "answers":[ "みなさん" ] },
	{ "question": "目", "answers":[ "め" ] },
	{ "question": "着く", "answers":[ "つく" ] },
	{ "question": "着る", "answers":[ "きる" ] },
	{ "question": "知る", "answers":[ "しる" ] },
	{ "question": "短い", "answers":[ "みじかい" ] },
	{ "question": "私", "answers":[ "わたし" ] },
	{ "question": "空", "answers":[ "そら" ] },
	{ "question": "窓", "answers":[ "まど" ] },
	{ "question": "立つ", "answers":[ "たつ" ] },
	{ "question": "答える", "answers":[ "こたえる" ] },
	{ "question": "箱", "answers":[ "はこ" ] },
	{ "question": "紅茶", "answers":[ "こうちゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "紙", "answers":[ "かみ" ] },
	{ "question": "細い", "answers":[ "ほそい" ] },
	{ "question": "終る", "answers":[ "おわる" ] },
	{ "question": "結婚", "answers":[ "けっこん" ] },
	{ "question": "結構", "answers":[ "けっこう" ] },
	{ "question": "絵", "answers":[ "え" ] },
	{ "question": "緑", "answers":[ "みどり" ] },
	{ "question": "締める", "answers":[ "しめる" ] },
	{ "question": "練習", "answers":[ "れんしゅう" ] },
	{ "question": "置く", "answers":[ "おく" ] },
	{ "question": "習う", "answers":[ "ならう" ] },
	{ "question": "耳", "answers":[ "みみ" ] },
	{ "question": "聞く", "answers":[ "きく" ] },
	{ "question": "肉", "answers":[ "にく" ] },
	{ "question": "背", "answers":[ "せ" ] },
	{ "question": "背広", "answers":[ "せびろ" ] },
	{ "question": "脱ぐ", "answers":[ "ぬぐ" ] },
	{ "question": "自分", "answers":[ "じぶん" ] },
	{ "question": "自動車", "answers":[ "じどうしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "自転車", "answers":[ "じてんしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "色", "answers":[ "いろ" ] },
	{ "question": "花", "answers":[ "はな" ] },
	{ "question": "花瓶", "answers":[ "かびん" ] },
	{ "question": "若い", "answers":[ "わかい" ] },
	{ "question": "英語", "answers":[ "えいご" ] },
	{ "question": "茶色", "answers":[ "ちゃいろ" ] },
	{ "question": "荷物", "answers":[ "にもつ" ] },
	{ "question": "葉書", "answers":[ "はがき" ] },
	{ "question": "薬", "answers":[ "くすり" ] },
	{ "question": "行く", "answers":[ "いく", "ゆく" ] },
	{ "question": "西", "answers":[ "にし" ] },
	{ "question": "見る", "answers":[ "みる" ] },
	{ "question": "見える", "answers":[ "みえる" ] },
	{ "question": "見せる", "answers":[ "みせる" ] },
	{ "question": "覚える", "answers":[ "おぼえる" ] },
	{ "question": "角", "answers":[ "かど", "つの" ] },
	{ "question": "言う", "answers":[ "いう" ] },
	{ "question": "言葉", "answers":[ "ことば" ] },
	{ "question": "話", "answers":[ "はなし" ] },
	{ "question": "話す", "answers":[ "はなす" ] },
	{ "question": "誕生日", "answers":[ "たんじょうび" ] },
	{ "question": "読む", "answers":[ "よむ" ] },
	{ "question": "警官", "answers":[ "けいかん" ] },
	{ "question": "豚肉", "answers":[ "ぶたにく" ] },
	{ "question": "財布", "answers":[ "さいふ" ] },
	{ "question": "買い物", "answers":[ "かいもの" ] },
	{ "question": "買う", "answers":[ "かう" ] },
	{ "question": "貸す", "answers":[ "かす" ] },
	{ "question": "質問", "answers":[ "しつもん" ] },
	{ "question": "走る", "answers":[ "はしる" ] },
	{ "question": "起きる", "answers":[ "おきる" ] },
	{ "question": "車", "answers":[ "くるま" ] },
	{ "question": "軽い", "answers":[ "かるい" ] },
	{ "question": "辞書", "answers":[ "じしょ" ] },
	{ "question": "辺", "answers":[ "へん" ] },
	{ "question": "近い", "answers":[ "ちかい" ] },
	{ "question": "近く", "answers":[ "ちかく" ] },
	{ "question": "返す", "answers":[ "かえす" ] },
	{ "question": "速い", "answers":[ "はやい" ] },
	{ "question": "遅い", "answers":[ "おそい" ] },
	{ "question": "道", "answers":[ "みち" ] },
	{ "question": "違う", "answers":[ "ちがう" ] },
	{ "question": "遠い", "answers":[ "とおい" ] },
	{ "question": "部屋", "answers":[ "へや" ] },
	{ "question": "郵便局", "answers":[ "ゆうびんきょく" ] },
	{ "question": "重い", "answers":[ "おもい" ] },
	{ "question": "野菜", "answers":[ "やさい" ] },
	{ "question": "金曜日", "answers":[ "きんようび" ] },
	{ "question": "鉛筆", "answers":[ "えんぴつ" ] },
	{ "question": "銀行", "answers":[ "ぎんこう" ] },
	{ "question": "長い", "answers":[ "ながい" ] },
	{ "question": "門", "answers":[ "かど", "もん" ] },
	{ "question": "閉まる", "answers":[ "しまる" ] },
	{ "question": "閉める", "answers":[ "しめる" ] },
	{ "question": "階段", "answers":[ "かいだん" ] },
	{ "question": "雑誌", "answers":[ "ざっし" ] },
	{ "question": "難しい", "answers":[ "むずかしい" ] },
	{ "question": "雨", "answers":[ "あめ" ] },
	{ "question": "雪", "answers":[ "ゆき" ] },
	{ "question": "電気", "answers":[ "でんき" ] },
	{ "question": "電話", "answers":[ "でんわ" ] },
	{ "question": "電車", "answers":[ "でんしゃ" ] },
	{ "question": "静か", "answers":[ "しずか" ] },
	{ "question": "音楽", "answers":[ "おんがく" ] },
	{ "question": "頭", "answers":[ "あたま" ] },
	{ "question": "頼む", "answers":[ "たのむ" ] },
	{ "question": "風", "answers":[ "かぜ" ] },
	{ "question": "飛ぶ", "answers":[ "とぶ" ] },
	{ "question": "飛行機", "answers":[ "ひこうき" ] },
	{ "question": "食べる", "answers":[ "たべる" ] },
	{ "question": "食べ物", "answers":[ "たべもの" ] },
	{ "question": "食堂", "answers":[ "しょくどう" ] },
	{ "question": "飲み物", "answers":[ "のみもの" ] },
	{ "question": "飲む", "answers":[ "のむ" ] },
	{ "question": "駅", "answers":[ "えき" ] },
	{ "question": "高い", "answers":[ "たかい" ] },
	{ "question": "魚", "answers":[ "さかな", "うお" ] },
	{ "question": "鳥", "answers":[ "とり" ] },
	{ "question": "鳴く", "answers":[ "なく" ] },
	{ "question": "何", "answers":[ "なに", "なん" ] },
	{ "question": "黄色", "answers":[ "きいろ" ] },
	{ "question": "黄色い", "answers":[ "きいろい" ] },
	{ "question": "黒", "answers":[ "くろ" ] },
	{ "question": "赤ちゃん", "answers": [ "あかちゃん" ] },
	{ "question": "黒い", "answers":[ "くろい" ] }
]
}
